(electronic beeping)
(gentle music)
♪ A scrub is a guy that thinks he's fly ♪
♪ And is also known as a busta ♪
♪ Always talkin' about what he wants ♪
♪ And just sits on his broke ass ♪
♪ So no, I don't want your number ♪
♪ No, I don't want to give you mine and ♪
♪ No, I don't want to meet you nowhere ♪
♪ No, I don't want none of your time and ♪
♪ No, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ Well a scrub checkin' me ♪
♪ But his game is kinda weak ♪
♪ And I know that he cannot approach me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm looking like class,
and he's looking like trash ♪
♪ Can't get with a deadbeat ass ♪
♪ So no, I don't want your number ♪
♪ No, I don't want to give you mine and ♪
♪ No, I don't want to meet you nowhere ♪
♪ No, I don't want none of your time ♪
♪ No, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ If you don't have a
car and you're walking ♪
♪ Oh yes son, I'm talking to you ♪
♪ If you live at home with your momma ♪
♪ If you have a shorty
that you don't show love ♪
♪ Oh yes son, I'm talking to you ♪
♪ Wanna get me with no money ♪
♪ Oh no, I don't want no ♪
♪ No scrub, no scrub, no love ♪
♪ No scrub, no scrub ♪
♪ No scrub ♪
♪ No, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ See, if you can't spatially
expand my horizons ♪
♪ Then that leaves you in the
class with scrubs never risin' ♪
♪ I don't find it surprisin'
if you don't have the Gs ♪
♪ To please me and bounce from
here to the coast of overseas ♪
♪ So, let me give you
somethin' to think about ♪
♪ Inundate your mind with
intentions to turn you out ♪
♪ Can't forget the focus on
the picture in front of me ♪
♪ You as clear as DVD
on digital TV screens ♪
♪ Satisfy my appetite with
somethin' spectacular ♪
♪ Check your vernacular, and
then I'll get back to ya ♪
♪ With diamond-like precision,
insatiable is what I envision ♪
♪ Can't detect acquisition
from your friend's Expedition ♪
♪ Mister Big Willy, if
you really wanna know ♪
♪ Ask Chilli, could I be
a silly ho, not really ♪
♪ T-Boz and all my senoritas
are steppin' on your FILAs ♪
♪ But you don't hear me though ♪
♪ No, I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla at me ♪
♪ I don't want no scrub ♪
♪ A scrub is a guy that
can't get no love from me ♪
♪ Hangin' out the passenger side ♪
♪ Of his best friend's ride ♪
♪ Trying to holla ♪